{
    "id": "191555a5e2b845cd80a20441dfeffb30",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Who is this present ………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "916baeea34024d4cbddef61004616395"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am really angry ……………. you.",
            "description": "With is used after a number of adjectives which say how people are feeling towards others.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "faa5ab99e2374d97bfb0fd8046d3eec2"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………… all this work to do, I won’t have time to take a holiday.",
            "description": "With can introduce the accompanying circumstances.",
            "answers": [
                "With",
                "For",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "224cecf5455447f29e81a67f5633230c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was talking ……………. such a low voice that I could not hear anything.",
            "description": "We say ‘in a voice’.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3cae521fb8af45cab4aa83b5f9fb855e"
        },
        {
            "question": "If we go …………… car, we will reach there before sunset.",
            "description": "We use 'by' with car, train, bus etc.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "with",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0ab2adb8349d45e1abdc7ef19107f997"
        },
        {
            "question": "The actress has always been very nice ……………. her fans.",
            "description": "Words like kind, nice, polite and rude are followed by to.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d9d83464e1fa414db8305d7189ab8208"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………….friends like you, who needs enemies?",
            "description": "With can mean 'because there are/is.'",
            "answers": [
                "With",
                "Without",
                "For",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3802dc1e15704e3fb6b72971c8067b75"
        },
        {
            "question": "What kind of movies are you interested …………..?",
            "description": "We say 'interested in something'.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1fa370c718d74d4a88cc5a3444fe3199"
        },
        {
            "question": "The cottage is pleasant to live …………….",
            "description": "We 'live in' a cottage or a house. ",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "de00b5aed07c43e99360a39a493a58d0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which flight is she travelling ……………?",
            "description": "People travel 'on a flight'",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e5289cdf115445f9ae7c6370915a67ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are the only woman I have ever been in love…………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "in",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bd890ac6dd544cd48afc51623a53ac99"
        },
        {
            "question": "That is what I am afraid ……………..",
            "description": "We say 'afraid of something'.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "cd4fc73c0f32407785c0225ec3cbfec4"
        }
    ]
}